Guide to the James H. Gillespie Papers, 1943-1996
Gillespie, James H. papers, 1943-1996
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
James H. Gillespie Papers, 1943-1996
24-02-3293
James H. Gillespie.
1.0 cubic ft.
Biographical material, published material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Biographical material, reprints and several editions of Hagan and Bruner's Infectious Diseases of Domestic Animals, the seminal veterinary text authored by William Arthur Hagan and Dorsey William Bruner, et al.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
James H. Gillespie is Professor of Veterinary Microbiology, Emeritus, Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Biographical material, reprints and several editions of Hagan and Bruner's Infectious Diseases of Domestic Animals, the seminal veterinary text authored by William Arthur Hagan and Dorsey William Bruner, et al.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gillespie, James Howard.; Hagan, William Arthur, 1893-1963.; Bruner, Dorsey William, 1906-.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine-- Faculty.
Subjects:
Veterinary microbiology--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
PROVENANCE
Gift of James H. Gillespie.
CONTAINER LIST
- Biography, 1987 (Folder 1)
- Reprints, 1954-1976, n.d. (Folder 2)
- List of Corrections for Hagan, 6th edition, ca. 1978-1981 (Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous, 1986, 1996, n.d. (Folder 4)
- Hagan, William Arthur. The Infectious Diseases of Domestic Animals. Ithaca: Comstock, 1943.
- Bruner, Dorsey William and James Howard Gillespie. Hagan's Infectious Diseases of Domestic Animals. 5th ed. Ithaca: Comstock, 1966.
- Bruner, Dorsey William and James Howard Gillespie. Hagan's Infectious Diseases of Domestic Animals. 6th ed. Ithaca: Comstock, 1973.
- Bruner, Dorsey W. and James H. Gillespie. Hagan Malattie Infettive degli Animali Domestici. Italian translation of the 5th American ed. Faenza: Fratelli Lega Editori, 1973.
- Timoney, John F, James H. Gillespie, et al. Hagan & Bruner Microbiologia e Malattie Infettive degli Animali Domestici. 3d Italian ed. Translation of the 8th American ed. Bologna: Editoriale Grasso, 1995.
- Bruner, Dorsey William and James Howard Gillespie. Hagan Enfermedades Infecciosas de los Animals Domesticos. 3d Mexican ed. Translation of the 5th American ed. Mexico: La Prensa Medica Mexicana, 1970.
- Gillespie, James Howard and John Francis Timoney. Hagan Y Bruner Enfermedades Infecciosas de los Animals Domesticos. 4th Mexican ed. Translation of the 7th American ed. Mexico: La Prensa Medica Mexicana, 1983.
- Bruner, Dorsey William and James Howard Gillespie. [Hagan's Infectious Diseases of Domestic Animals.] Japanese Translation of the 6th American ed. Tokyo: Ishiyaku Publishers, ca. 1975.